{
    "Questions": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Who is most likely to name their variable 'Pizza'?",
        "answer1": "David",
        "answer2": "Sean",
        "answer3": "Eni",
        "answer4": "Adam",
        "correctanswer": "answer1"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Who went to nursing school?",
        "answer1": "Shiraf",
        "answer2": "Eni",
        "answer3": "Laura",
        "answer4": "Marcus",
        "correctanswer": "answer2"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Who owns (and wears to class) a sweathshirt that says KALE...not YALE?",
        "answer1": "Laura",
        "answer2": "Amy",
        "answer3": "Brenna",
        "answer4": "James",
        "correctanswer": "answer3"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Who is most likely to be good at cappuccino foam art?",
        "answer1": "David",
        "answer2": "Alex",
        "answer3": "Eni",
        "answer4": "James",
        "correctanswer": "answer4"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Who likes animae more than Adam?",
        "answer1": "Marcus",
        "answer2": "Sean",
        "answer3": "Brenna",
        "answer4": "Shiraf",
        "correctanswer": "answer1"
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Who is learning Arabic?",
        "answer1": "Shiraf",
        "answer2": "Laura",
        "answer3": "Eni",
        "answer4": "David",
        "correctanswer": "answer2"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Who recently moved and lost internet for a few days?",
        "answer1": "Marcus",
        "answer2": "James",
        "answer3": "Shiraf",
        "answer4": "Amy",
        "correctanswer": "answer3"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Who lost Alex money with bad (HORRIBLE!!!) stock advice?",
        "answer1": "David",
        "answer2": "Amy",
        "answer3": "Brenna",
        "answer4": "Sean",
        "correctanswer": "answer4"
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Who got kicked out of their partner's parents' house?",
        "answer1": "Adam",
        "answer2": "Alex",
        "answer3": "Laura",
        "answer4": "Amy",
        "correctanswer": "answer1"
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Who is most likely to ask stupid questions?",
        "answer1": "Shiraf",
        "answer2": "Alex",
        "answer3": "James",
        "answer4": "Brenna",
        "correctanswer": "answer2"
      },
      {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Who got engaged in Freiburg, Germany?",
        "answer1": "Eni",
        "answer2": "Brenna",
        "answer3": "Amy",
        "answer4": "Shiraf",
        "correctanswer": "answer3"
      }
    ]
}